Mateo Acevedo Vargas



I am a full stack developer with experience in modern site development, interface design

friendly and intuitive. My goal is to be part of a company where I can put in practice all my knowledge, that gives me the opportunity to achieve all my goals

traced, and that it offers me the opportunity to grow in the area, both professionally, personally and intellectually.

Software Developer

Personal Info

Country

Dominican Republic Santo Domingo

Phone

809-216-0246

E-mail

mateoacevedo809@gmail.com

Website

matiux.netlify.app

Technical Skills

- Javascript
- HTML
- CSS
- ReactJS
- VueJS
- Typescript
- NodeJS
- · Adobe Coldfusion
- NextJS
- TailwindCSS

Professional Skills

- · Effective communication
- Team Work
- · Problem Solving
- · Good time management

Experience

²⁰²⁰⁻¹⁰ - Full Stack Developer (VueJS, NodeJS)

2022-04 RFCG Computer, Santo Domingo, DR

- Worked with the development team to refine the debugging process
- · Responsible for creating, improving, and developing IT project s

Full Stack Developer (Adobe Coldfusion)

present CONAPE (Consejo Nacional de la Persona Envejeciente), Santo Domingo, DR

· Worked with the development team to refine the debugging process

•

2023-04 - Front-End Developer (NextJS with TailwindCSS)

present HarPer SRL, Santo Domingo, DR

- · Worked with the development team to refine the debugging process and creating new systems
- · Responsible for creating, improving, and developing systems

Education

2017-12 - Senior Technician in Software Development,

instituto Tecnico Superior Comunitario, ITSC

2020-03 - **C# Web Developer**

• Instituto Tecnologico de las Americas, ITLA

Interests

- · Drawing and painting
- · Play Videogames
- · Play Sports Like Basketball, etc.

Languages

Spanish

English Basic-Intermediate

Dasic-intermedia

Mativ

Native